(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-16T01:09:17.112200",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" - Now accepting new members!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
GUM & DROP - Now available on digital platforms!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event PAJAMA PARTY Vol.2
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: Pajama Party Vol. 2
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1st EP Travelogue
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 2nd Live Project: ALLEGRO
Once Upon a Stellar OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP
Once Upon a Stellar - Official Goods Lineup
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" - Now accepting new members!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
GUM & DROP - Now available on digital platforms!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event PAJAMA PARTY Vol.2
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: Pajama Party Vol. 2
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1st EP Travelogue
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 2nd Live Project: ALLEGRO
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live Project: Allegra
Once Upon a Stellar - オフィシャルグッズラインナップ
Once Upon a Stellar - Official Goods Lineup
星街すいせい オフィシャルファンクラブ「星詠み」新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" - Now Accepting New Members!
星街すいせい「GUM&DROP」好評配信中！
Hoshimachi Suisei "GUM&DROP" - Now Available Stream!
星街すいせい オフィシャルイベント「PAJAMA PARTY Vol.2」
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event "Pajama Party Vol. 2"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP「travelogue」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP "travelogue"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live Project: Allegra
Once Upon a Stellar - オフィシャルグッズラインナップ
Once Upon a Stellar - Official Goods Lineup
星街すいせい オフィシャルファンクラブ「星詠み」新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" - Now Accepting New Members!
星街すいせい「GUM&DROP」好評配信中！
Hoshimachi Suisei "GUM&DROP" - Now Available Stream!
星街すいせい オフィシャルイベント「PAJAMA PARTY Vol.2」
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event "Pajama Party Vol. 2"
星街すいせい Official Event 「Pajama Party Vol.2」
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event "Pajama Party Vol.2"
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1st EP 「travelogue」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP "travelogue"
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 2nd LIVE PROJECT: ALLEGRO
Once Upon a Stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
Once Upon a Stellar - Official Goods Lineup
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 「星詠み」 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" - Now Accepting New Members!
「GUM & DROP」 好評配信中！
"GUM & DROP" Now Streaming!
星街すいせい Official Event 「Pajama Party Vol.2」
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event "Pajama Party Vol.2"
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1st EP 「travelogue」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP "travelogue"
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 2nd LIVE PROJECT: ALLEGRO
Once Upon a Stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
Once Upon a Stellar - Official Goods Lineup
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 「星詠み」 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" - Now Accepting New Members!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi": Now Accepting New Members!
『GUM & DROP』 好評配信中！
"GUM & DROP" Now Streaming!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event 「Pajama Party Vol.2」
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: Pajama Party Vol. 2
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP 『Travelogue』
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP "Travelogue"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live Project: ALLEGRO
「Once Upon a Stellar」 オフィシャルグッズラインナップ
"Once Upon a Stellar" Official Goods Lineup
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 「星詠み」 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi": Now Accepting New Members!
『GUM & DROP』 好評配信中！
"GUM & DROP" Now Streaming!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event 「Pajama Party Vol.2」
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: Pajama Party Vol. 2
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP 『Travelogue』
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP "Travelogue"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live Project: ALLEGRO
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live Project: Allegria
Once Upon a Stellar - Official Goods Lineup -
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" - Now Accepting New Members!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
GUM & DROP - Now Available for Streaming!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: Pajama Party Vol. 2
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP "Travelogue"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live Project: Allegria
Once Upon a Stellar - Official Goods Lineup -
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" - Now Accepting New Members!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
GUM & DROP - Now Available for Streaming!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: Pajama Party Vol. 2
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event Pajama Party Vol.2
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP 「Travelogue I」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP "Travelogue I"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live Project 「ALLEGRA」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live Project "ALLEGRA"
Once Upon a Stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 「星詠み」 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" - Now Accepting New Members!
「GUM & DROP」 好評配信中！
"GUM & DROP" - Available Now!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event Pajama Party Vol.2
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP 「Travelogue I」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP "Travelogue I"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live Project 「ALLEGRA」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live Project "ALLEGRA"
Once Upon a Stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 「星詠み」 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" - Now Accepting New Members!
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
GUM & DROP - Now Available!
Pajama Party Vol.2 With HOSHIMACHI SUISEI
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1st EP 『Travelogue』
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP "Travelogue"
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 2nd LIVE PROJECT: ALLEGRO
Once Upon a Stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
Once Upon a Stellar - Official Goods Lineup
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" - Now Accepting New Members!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
GUM & DROP - Now Available!
Pajama Party Vol.2 With HOSHIMACHI SUISEI
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1st EP 『Travelogue』
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP "Travelogue"
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 2nd LIVE PROJECT: ALLEGRO
(2ND LIVE) PROJECT: ALLEGRO
Once Upon a Stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
Once Upon a Stellar: Official Goods Lineup
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub Hoshiyomi: Accepting new members!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
GUM & DROP: Available now!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event Pajama Party Vol.2
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: Pajama Party Vol. 2
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1st EP travelogue (TRACK LIST)
(2ND LIVE) PROJECT: ALLEGRO
Once Upon a Stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
Once Upon a Stellar: Official Goods Lineup
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub Hoshiyomi: Accepting new members!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
GUM & DROP: Available now!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event Pajama Party Vol.2
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: Pajama Party Vol. 2
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event 「Pajama Party vol.2」
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event "Pajama Party vol.2"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP 「travelogue I」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP "travelogue I"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd LIVE Project 「ALLEGRO」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd LIVE Project "ALLEGRO"
Once Upon a Stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 「星詠み」 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" - Now accepting new members!
「GUM & DROP」 好評配信中！
"GUM & DROP" - Now Available on Streaming Platforms!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event 「Pajama Party vol.2」
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event "Pajama Party vol.2"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP 「travelogue I」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP "travelogue I"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd LIVE Project 「ALLEGRO」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd LIVE Project "ALLEGRO"
Once Upon a Stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 「星詠み」 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" - Now accepting new members!
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
GUM & DROP - Now available on streaming services!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event PAJAMA PARTY Vol. 2
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP 「travelogue」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP "travelogue"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live Project 「ALLEGRIA」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live Project: ALLEGRIA
Once Upon a Stellar オフィシャルグッズラインナップ
Once Upon a Stellar Official Goods Lineup
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" - Now accepting new members!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
GUM & DROP - Now available on streaming services!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event PAJAMA PARTY Vol. 2
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP 「travelogue」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP "travelogue"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live Project 「ALLEGRIA」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live Project: ALLEGRIA
Midnight Grand Orchestra (2ND LIVE) PROJECT: ALLEGRO
Once Upon a Stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" Now Accepting New Members!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
GUM & DROP - Now Available for Streaming!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event PAJAMA PARTY Vol.2
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: Pajama Party Vol. 2
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP travelogue
Midnight Grand Orchestra (2ND LIVE) PROJECT: ALLEGRO
Once Upon a Stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" Now Accepting New Members!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
GUM & DROP - Now Available for Streaming!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event PAJAMA PARTY Vol.2
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: Pajama Party Vol. 2
星街すいせい Official Event PAJAMA PARTY Vol.2
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event PAJAMA PARTY Vol.2]
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP 『Travelogue』
[Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP "Travelogue"]
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live Project: ALLEGRIA
Once Upon a Stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" - Now Accepting New Members!]
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
[GUM & DROP - Now Available!]
星街すいせい Official Event PAJAMA PARTY Vol.2
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event PAJAMA PARTY Vol.2]
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP 『Travelogue』
[Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP "Travelogue"]
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live Project: ALLEGRIA
Once Upon a Stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" - Now Accepting New Members!]
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshizomi" - Now Accepting New Members!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
GUM & DROP - Now Available on Streaming Platforms!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event PAJAMA PARTY Vol.2
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP Travelogue
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live Project ALLEGRO
Once Upon a Stellar OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshizomi" - Now Accepting New Members!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
GUM & DROP - Now Available on Streaming Platforms!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event PAJAMA PARTY Vol.2
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP Travelogue
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live Project ALLEGRO
(2ND LIVE) PROJECT: ALLEGRA
Once Upon a Stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
[Once Upon a Stellar - Official Goods Lineup]
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub Hoshimiyomi: Now Accepting New Members!]
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
[Gum & Drop: Now Available!]
Pajama PARTY Vol.2 With HOSHIMACHI SUISEI
[Pajama Party Vol. 2 with Hoshimachi Suisei]
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP Travelogue
(2ND LIVE) PROJECT: ALLEGRA
Once Upon a Stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
[Once Upon a Stellar - Official Goods Lineup]
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub Hoshimiyomi: Now Accepting New Members!]
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
[Gum & Drop: Now Available!]
Pajama PARTY Vol.2 With HOSHIMACHI SUISEI
[Pajama Party Vol. 2 with Hoshimachi Suisei]
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event PAJAMA PARTY Vol.2
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: Pajama Party Vol. 2]
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1st EP 『travelogue』
[Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP: Travelogue]
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 2nd LIVE PROJECT: ALLEGRIA
Once Upon a Stellar OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub 'Hoshiyomi' - Accepting New Members Now!]
GUM&DROP 好評配信中！
[GUM & DROP - Now Available on Streaming Services!]
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event PAJAMA PARTY Vol.2
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: Pajama Party Vol. 2]
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1st EP 『travelogue』
[Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP: Travelogue]
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 2nd LIVE PROJECT: ALLEGRIA
Once Upon a Stellar OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub 'Hoshiyomi' - Accepting New Members Now!]
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" - Now Accepting New Members!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
GUM & DROP - Now Available!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event PAJAMA PARTY vol.2
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP 「travelogue」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP "travelogue"
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live 「ALLEGRIA」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 2nd Live "ALLEGRIA"
Once Upon a Stellar OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" - Now Accepting New Members!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
GUM & DROP - Now Available!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event PAJAMA PARTY vol.2
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP 「travelogue」
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP "travelogue"
本日は、アイドリッシュセブン LIVE PERFORMANCE 2024 “Once Upon a A Stage” にご来場いただきまして、誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much for attending IDOLiSH7 LIVE PERFORMANCE 2024 "Once Upon a A Stage" today.
開演に先立ちまして、皆様にいくつかのお願いとご案内がございます。
Before the performance begins, we have a few requests and announcements for you.
皆様にお願い申し上げます。
May I have your attention, please.
お客様の安全確保のため、
For the safety of all guests,
お席を離れての鑑賞はご遠慮いただいております。
please remain in your assigned seats during the show.
あらかじめご了承ください。
Thank you for your understanding.
また、本公演の演出の都合上、
Also, due to stage production reasons,
開演いたしますと、しばらくの間、
once the performance starts, for a brief period,
お席へのご案内をお止めいただく場合がございます。
guidance to your seat may be temporarily paused.
お早めにお手洗いなどお済ませの上、
Please use the restrooms early
お座席にてお待ちください。
and wait at your seat.
本日の公演は、記録撮影のため、
Today's performance will be recorded,
会場内にカメラが設置されております。
so cameras are installed throughout the venue.
客席の様子が写真・映像に
Members of the audience
映り込む場合がございます。
may be captured in photos or video footage.
会場内の写真や映像は、
Photos and footage taken in the venue
公開されることがございます。
may be published or broadcast.
印刷物、メディア等に露出・掲載される場合がございます。
They may be featured in print media or online.
以上をご了承の上、ご鑑賞いただきますようお願いいたします。
Please be aware of this and enjoy the show.
場内での許可のない写真撮影、
Unauthorized photography,
録音、録画、ならびに配信行為は固くお断りいたします。
audio or video recording, and streaming are strictly prohibited.
また、指示のない過度な応援や、
Also, excessive cheering without instruction,
指示のない声を出す行為、
shouting,
周囲のお客様のご迷惑となる行為はお控えください。
or any behavior that disturbs others is strictly forbidden.
場内でのお食事、飲酒、ならびに
Eating, drinking alcohol,
喫煙はお断りいたします。
and smoking inside the venue are prohibited.
本日は、熱中症予防のため、
However, to prevent heat stroke today,
水分補給を目的とした蓋の閉まる容器に入ったお飲み物のみ
only drinks in sealable containers meant for hydration
お持ち込みいただけます。
may be brought into the venue.
演出の妨げや、周りのお客様の
To avoid disrupting the performance
ご迷惑となりますので、客席内での
or bothering other guests,
携帯電話のご使用はお控えください。
please refrain from using mobile phones in the seating area.
アラームなど音の出る機器の電源はお切りいただくか、
Please turn off devices that make noise, such as alarms,
マナーモードに設定していただきますようお願いいたします。
or switch them to silent mode.
あらかじめ体調のすぐれないお客様、
If you feel unwell
または、気分が悪くなりましたら、
or experience a sudden change in health,
無理をなさらず、
please do not push yourself
お近くのスタッフまでお申し出ください。
and inform a nearby staff member.
あ、照明さん
Ah, lighting operator...
もうちょっと右下ー
A little more to the bottom right.
あ、もっと左下ー
Ah, more to the bottom left.
あ、そうそうそうそう
Ah, yes, yes, yes, yes!
いい感じー
That looks great~
じゃ、スイッチ、オン！
Now then, switch... ON!
みんなー！ヤッホー！
Everyone~! Yoo-hoo!
すいちゃんー！よー！
It's Suichan~!
星詠みのみんなー
To all the Hoshiyomi,
今日が初めてのみんなー
and everyone here for the first time today,
会いに来てくれて、ありがとうー！
thank you so much for coming to see me!
いやー、もうすぐ始まるんだけど、その前に！
Man, the show is starting soon, but before that!
おいしょ！
Heave-ho!
ライブマナー！
Live Manners!
ということで、
So then,
すいちゃんからみんなへ、ライブを楽しむためのお願い事が
here are three requests from Suichan
3つあるー！
to help everyone enjoy the live!
まず1つ目！
First off, number one!
ライブ中は、
During the live,
撮影・録音はできないよ！
photography and recording are strictly prohibited!
今日しか見られない景色、一緒に楽しもう！
Let's enjoy this view that can only be seen today together!
次！2つ目！
Next! Number two!
応援してくれるのは、すっごく嬉しい！
I'm super happy that you're cheering for me!
でも、周りが見えなくなると...
But if you lose sight of your surroundings...
すいちゃんかわいいの〜！すいちゃん今日もかわいいの〜！
Suichan is so cute~! Suichan is cute today too~!
すいちゃーん！今日も可愛いー！
Suichaaaannn! You're cute today too!
すいちゃーん！すいちゃーん！すいちゃーん！
Suichan! Suichan! Suichan!
うわー！すいちゃーん！今日も可愛いー！
Woah! Suichan! You're cute today too!
ということで、周りがびっくりしちゃうような大声や行動は、ダメー！
So, yelling or acting in a way that startles people around you is a big no-no!
あと、「すいちゃんは今日もかわいい！」コールも、
Also, saving the "Suichan is cute today too!" chant
すいちゃんが合図するまで、取っておいてね！
until Suichan gives the signal is a must!
そして3つ目！
And number three!
みんな、ペンライト持ってるー？
Everyone, do you have your penlights?
見せて見せてー！
Show me, show me~!
ライブが始まったら、もっと凄くなるね！
Once the live starts, it's gonna look even more amazing!
でも、使うときにはルールがあるー！
But there are rules when using them!
改造ペンライトや
Modified penlights,
26cmを超えるもの、
penlights over 26 cm,
眩しすぎるものは、
or high-brightness ones
使っちゃダメ！
are strictly forbidden!
みんなでルールを守って、楽しいライブにするよ！
Let's all follow the rules and make this a fun live concert!
協力してくれるー？
Will you all cooperate with me?
じゃあ、1回みんなでペンライト消すよー！
Alright, let me see everyone turn off their penlights once!
せーの！
Ready, go!
完璧！ありがとうー！
Perfect! Thank you~!
よし、これで準備OK！みんなもいけるー？
Alright, now we're all set! Is everyone ready too?
それじゃあ...
Well then...
始まるよー！
It's starting~!
STUDIO STELLAR
昔々...
Once upon a time...
キラキラと光る、不思議なお城に...
in a mysterious, sparkling castle...
星街すいせいという、女の子が住んでいました。
there lived a girl named Hoshimachi Suisei.
そこはまるで、おとぎ話の絵本から
It was a wonderful castle that looked as if
飛び出してきたような、素敵なお城です。
it had popped straight out of a fairy tale book.
夜になると、すいせいは窓辺で歌を歌います。
When night fell, Suisei would sing songs by the window.
花火が上がり
As fireworks shoot up,
みんなが笑顔になる
everyone flashes a smile.
キラキラと眩しい
Sparkling and dazzling,
星空のステージです
it's a stage under the starry sky.
痛天を刺す一ツ星の眩い
The dazzling light of a single star piercing the sky,
閃光に染まり散る
dyed in flash and scattering.
独り占めしたはずのここも
Even this place I was supposed to have to myself,
幕が下りれば Act 2
once the curtain falls, it's Act 2.
そこを退けて
Move out of the way.
譲れないわ My stage 邪魔しないで
I won't yield My stage, don't get in my way!
綺麗に Make up してさ 待ってる人がいるの
I put on nice makeup, someone is waiting for me.
OK?
ところでそちら どちら様ですか？
By the way, who might you be over there?
もういいですか？
Are you done already?
主役って大変だわ
Being the star is hard work!
Pop pop noise を消して
Erase the pop-pop noise,
目と目逸らさないでね
and don't avert your eyes, okay?
罪はどんな？ 賠償にはもううんざりだわ
What kind of sin? I'm already sick of compensation!
熱い Heart と Music 浴びて Spotlight
Basking in hot Heart and Music under the Spotlight!
たとえどんな闇も焦がすわ 騒がせ
No matter what darkness, I'll scorch it—make some noise!
1, 2... 乱れ乱れもう No time! Fuck off, bye!
1, 2... go wild, go wild, No time! Fuck off, bye!
あー 称賛絶賛ありがとう お気に召せば Let's go
Ah, thanks for the praise and acclaim! If you like it, Let's go!
嫉妬妬み嫉みから 嫌悪感に暇なんですか？
Free enough to wallow in jealousy, envy, and disgust?
やれ勝訴だ敗訴だの 殺すぞ？ ご機嫌よう
Winning or losing lawsuits—I'll kill you? Good day!
Pop pop flash を浴びて
Basking in the pop-pop flash,
耳を放さないでね
don't tune out your ears, okay?
惨劇の扉が開くように
As if opening the door to tragedy,
飛び込む世界は回る
the world I dive into spins round.
劇的な終わりに続くストーリー
A story leading to a dramatic ending—
誰のため歌い上げる？
for whom do I sing it out?
罪はどんな？ 敗北にはもううんざりだわ
What kind of sin? I'm sick of defeat already!
熱い Heart と Music 浴びて Spotlight
Basking in hot Heart and Music under the Spotlight!
たとえどんなエンディングが待ち受けていても
No matter what kind of ending awaits me,
1, 2... 乱れ乱れもう 騒がせ
1, 2... go wild, go wild, make some noise!
きっと思いは冷めない 心冷めない夢は
Surely these feelings won't cool down; an uncooling heart's dream
フィクションなんかじゃない
isn't just fiction!
たとえ誰が笑っても 嘲笑ってみせ
No matter who laughs, sneer right back at them!
Get out, No time! Fuck off, bye!
幕開け
The curtain rises!
立ち込める煙の中
Amidst the thick smoke,
歌い倒せ
sing until you drop!
Yeah
何万回だって教えてあげるね Next episode
I'll tell you tens of thousands of times: Next episode!
泥の味見ても 誰も You wonder girl
Even tasting mud, nobody can match You wonder girl!
うっとりさせたい 妄想見させたい
I want to enchant you, make you see wild delusions!
What's up? Bye bye, No line!
Siphon, Reach for とっておきの Treat 期待して
Siphon, Reach for—look forward to a special Treat!
時計の針よりも早いの Step
Faster than the clock hands—Step!
Wanna dance with me?
そうさ Perfect! 感傷論みたいね
That's right, Perfect! Sounds like sentimentalism, huh?
そうさ Perfect! 足りないよ
That's right, Perfect! It's not enough!
どうせ Sugar free! これ以上ないね
It's Sugar free anyway! Doesn't get better than this!
えーい Out on 狂乱 叫ぶわ
Hey, Out on frenzy, I'll scream!
Jewel L Kami Kami
Cool Yummy Yummy
Jewel L Kami Kami Let me give me a sign
囚われた私のドア
The door to my trapped self,
開くここからのマイスタイル
opens from here, my style.
マローアップでキープアップ 自分らしく spice in what you need
Mallow up and keep up, be true to yourself with spice in what you need.
甘いだけじゃない You are addiction
It's not just sweet—you are addiction.
See the reach for
とっておきのトリートメントさせて
Let me give you a special treatment.
ねぇ 響かせて 運命の音 罠の様に
Hey, let the sound of fate resound like a trap.
操作不能 感情みたいに
Uncontrollable, like my feelings,
強がりじゃ足りないよ
acting tough isn't enough.
ドレスアップでこれ以上ないね
Dressed up, it couldn't get any better.
Yeah Out of control
Sweet touch Every moment we touch Play your heart-b-beat 駆け引きの夜
Sweet touch, every moment we touch, play your heart-b-beat on this night of bargaining.
Tonight 金色のでたらめ 愛で満ちて
Tonight, filled with golden nonsense and love...
Jewel L Kami Kami Cool Yummy Yummy Jewel L Kami Kami Sugar-on-you Time
Jewel L Kami Kami Cool Yummy Yummy Jewel L Kami Kami Let me give me a sign
操作不能 感情みたいに
Uncontrollable, like my feelings,
強がりじゃ足りないよ
acting tough isn't enough.
ドレスアップでこれ以上ないね
Dressed up, it couldn't get any better.
Yeah Out of control
嘘で固めた感情が 歪んで溢れていた
Feelings hardened by lies were warped and overflowing.
理由もないこの衝動が 言わないロンリー ぼっちバイバイ
This baseless impulse says, "Goodbye to lonely, bye-bye to being alone."
あなたの目に映るかわいい私
The cute me reflected in your eyes...
この瞬間だけを望んで見つめ 壊れるまで
Wishing for and gazing at only this moment, until it breaks.
ロマンスを殺した
I killed romance.
タノシマナキャソン 今だけは アモーレ カモーレ 夜に甘えて
If you don't enjoy it, you lose. Just for now, Amore, Come on, indulge in the night.
罪深き口づけに 意味なんてないの 抑えられない情緒感
There's no meaning in a sinful kiss—this uncontrollable emotion.
私の思う愛情が にじんで汚れていた
The love I envisioned was smudged and tainted.
理屈ばかり頼んだ 正常な思考とバイバイ
Relying only on logic, goodbye to normal thinking.
大きくなったって愛なんて知らないわ
Even after growing up, I don't know what love is.
この瞬間だけをごまかしてみつめ 浮かれたのは ロマンスの果て
Deceiving and staring only at this moment, being swept away at the end of romance.
欲張りの世界は 病みつきのレメディ
A greedy world is an addictive remedy.
こんな私を飲ませたら ねぇ このまま連れ出してのめり込んで
If you make me drink this, hey, take me away like this and get absorbed.
さらってみせて
Sweep me off my feet.
この先も迷って迷って 狂うほど愛して
Keep getting lost from now on, love me to the point of madness.
ダメ、このままじゃ 行かないで
No, not like this... don't go.
タノシマナキャソン 今だけは ゆらして カモンネ 夜に踊って
If you don't enjoy it, you lose. Just for now, sway, come on, dance into the night.
取り繰り返し 意味なんてないの
Repeating it over and over... there's no meaning to it.
ハマらないで
Don't fall for it
どの道 悩みは
Either way, my worries
尽きないし
are endless, so
いっそ ノープランである
I'd rather have no plan at all.
世の中 騙すのも
Deceiving the world too,
はじめてからそう 孤独を伴っても
even if it comes with loneliness right from the start...
偶然じゃないって分かってんのって
Knowing that it's no coincidence,
じっとしたって
even if I stand still,
また同じとこで目を奪われて
my eyes are drawn to the exact same spot again.
なすがまま 風に任せて
Leaving it to fate, letting the wind carry it,
ウィスパー 虚しさ
whispering emptiness,
たしかにね
indeed it is.
そういうの待ってました
That's what I was waiting for.
大して変わんない フィニッシュライン
The finish line doesn't change much,
謎にキャパオーバー
mysteriously over capacity.
構いやしないよ 狂っている
I don't care, I'm going crazy
アンダッグデイ
Under day.
余計になんだって
Whatever extra it might be,
好きに思ってくれてもいい
feel free to think whatever you like.
なんだって伺ってるって
I know whatever is being gauged,
もう十分だ
it's already enough.
なんならセリフ返して
If anything, give me back my lines,
ハマらないで
don't fall for it.
なすがまま 風に任せて
Leaving it to fate, letting the wind carry it,
悪気はない
no hard feelings,
たしかにね
indeed.
そういうの待ってました
That's what I was waiting for.
大して変わんない フィニッシュライン
The finish line doesn't change much,
謎にキャパオーバー
mysteriously over capacity.
構いやしないよ 狂っている
I don't care, I'm going crazy
アンダッグデイ
Under day.
はじける心 メタリック
A bursting heart, metallic,
次の息を待ってる間の冷たさ
the coldness while waiting for the next breath,
嘘みたいな色してさ
with a color that feels like a lie,
つもりで居たい
I want to keep believing.
なすがまま 風に任せて
Leaving it to fate, letting the wind carry it,
ウィスパー 虚しさ
whispering emptiness,
たしかにね
indeed it is.
そういうの待ってました
That's what I was waiting for.
大して変わんない フィニッシュライン
The finish line doesn't change much,
謎にキャパオーバー
mysteriously over capacity.
構いやしないよ 狂っている
I don't care, I'm going crazy
アンダッグデイ
Under day.
まだ伺っていての アンダッグデイ
Still gauging, under day,
アンダッグデイ
under day,
under day.
はい！
Alright!
星街すいせい アリーナツアー 2026 "Once Upon a Stella"へ ようこそ！
Welcome to Hoshimachi Suisei Arena Tour 2026 "Once Upon a Stella"!
この城 すごくない？
Isn't this castle incredible?
すごい！そうだよね！
Amazing, right?!
え、あの、1日目も来ましたって人！
Um, who here came on Day 1 as well?
えー！？いやいやいや、多すぎ！
What?! No, no, way too many of you!
え、2日目から来ました、今日から来ましたって人！
Who came starting from Day 2—who came starting today?
おー、めっちゃいる！
Woah, there are so many of you!
え、じゃあ2日目から来た人はびっくりしたよね？
So those of you who came starting on Day 2 were surprised, right?
びっくり！そうだよね！
Surprised! Right?!
そう、あの、物販で販売してました、
Yeah, so, sold at the merch booth,
絵本『Once Upon a Stella 時をかける彗星のお城』の世界観、
the worldview of the picture book "Once Upon a Stella: The Time-Traveling Comet Castle",
物語を舞台に こういうお城を建てさせていただきまして、
setting the story on stage, we built a castle like this...
ライブ制作チームの皆さんと一緒にね
Together with everyone on the live production team,
この美術、演出、こだわって作らせていただきました！
we created this stage art and staging with meticulous care!
拍手！
Give them a round of applause!
あの、まあDay 1に来てた人もいっぱいいるということで
Um, well, since there are many people here who also came on Day 1,
Day 1ではこのお城のすごいところ
on Day 1, I talked about what's amazing about this castle...
この上の
This top part,
丸い
the round...
アストロラーベと呼ばれる、なんだっけ、星座表みたいな星座盤みたいなやつが
astrolabe thing, what was it, like a star chart or star disc...
「すごいよ」って話をしたんですけど、覚えてますか？Day 1来た人
I talked about how cool it was. Do you remember, those who came on Day 1?
Day 2の人も「覚えてるよ」って今言ったよね、絶対に
People here for Day 2 definitely just said, "I remember!" right now.
えー、じゃあちょっと、そうだよね、ちょっと違うこと言うならば
Well then, if I were to talk about something a bit different,
あの、バンドさんが城の上に立ってる！
the band members are standing on top of the castle!
すごくね？すごい！
Isn't that awesome? It's amazing!
そうだよね。はい、あの、いつものバンドメンバーでお送りしております
Right? Yes, we're bringing this to you with our usual band members.
皆さんよろしくお願いしますね
Everyone, please give them a big hand!
はい。えー、スタジオステラ設立して初めてのソロライブということで
Yes. Since this is the first solo live after establishing Studio Stella,
私もこだわり抜いてね
I really paid attention to every single detail,
もう毎日のようにスタッフさんと
and almost every day, with the staff members,
「すいせいさんこれ監修してください」「すいせいさんこれも監修...」
"Suisei-san, please supervise this!" "Suisei-san, supervise this too..."
「これすいせいさん監修...」「えっとこれはもっとこう...」「これはもっとこう...」「うんこれOK」
"Suisei-san, supervise this..." "Um, make this more like this... this like that... okay, this is fine!"
「これは何々」ってね、本当めっちゃ頑張って作ったんで
You know, we really worked super hard to build this,
ぜひ最後までこのライブを楽しんでいってください！
so please enjoy this live concert to the absolute fullest until the end!
昨日と違うことがあります。それは...
There's something different from yesterday. That is...
配信を見ているみんな！
Everyone watching the stream!
実はあの、ここらへんにコメントの雨が...
Actually, right around here, a rain of comments...
「イエーイ！」「うおー！」「見てるよー！」「はい！」「ふー！」「見てるー、すいちゃん！」
"Yay!" "Woah!" "I'm watching!" "Yes!" "Woo!" "We're watching, Sui-chan!"
っていうね、声が、はい、あります。楽しめているようです。
comments like that are appearing. Looks like they're enjoying it too.
YouTubeはね、あの、途中までしか見れませんので
You can only watch up to a certain point on YouTube,
ライブを最後まで見たい方は
so for those who want to watch the live until the end,
概要欄のSPWN、Z-aN、Huluで配信チケットをゲットしてください
please get a streaming ticket on SPWN, Z-aN, or Hulu linked in the description.
え、なんとね、でもね
But guess what,
いつもだったらここで「ごめんなさい、ここで...」
usually, around here I'd say, "Sorry, but right here..."
「チラ見せは終了」って言うじゃないですか
"the sneak peek ends!" right?
なんと今日はここでは終わらない！
But surprisingly, today it doesn't end here!
すごいよね。じゃあどこで終わるのか？ちょっとDay 1来た人はね、「ここじゃね？」って予想しながらね、見てください
Amazing, right? So where will it end? Those who came on Day 1, try guessing "Is it here?" as you watch.
ということで、ちょっとお忘れじゃないですか？
So, haven't you forgotten a little something?
恒例のあれ、やっちゃいますよ？
Shall we do that usual thing?
アリーナの皆さん、行けますかー？！
Everyone in the Arena section, are you ready?!
レベル3の皆さん、行けますかー？！
Everyone on Level 3, are you ready?!
レベル5の皆さん、行けますかー？！
Everyone on Level 5, are you ready?!
レベル7の人、行けますかー？！
Everyone on Level 7, are you ready?!
いいね！見えてるからね！「遠いな」とか思ってるんでしょ？
Nice! I can see you! You're thinking "It's so far," right?
レベル7もレベル5もレベル3もね、アリーナの後ろも見えてますからね！
I can see Level 7, Level 5, Level 3, and the back of the Arena clearly!
気抜いちゃダメですよ！
Don't let your guard down!
あ、配信のみんなも行けるー？！
Ah, everyone on stream, are you ready too?!
ありがとうございます、配信の皆さんの分も
Thank you! That was for everyone on stream too.
それでは、彗星のごとく現れたスターの原石！バーチャルアイドル星街すいせいです！
Alright! Then... A rough diamond of a star that appeared like a comet! I'm virtual idol Hoshimachi Suisei!
すいちゃんは～？
Sui-chan is...?
まだ行けるな...
You can still do better than that...
え？ちょっと今日みんな雨降ったから湿気られちゃってんじゃないの？ねえ？
Huh? Did the rain make everyone a bit dampened today? Huh?
吹き飛ばそう！
Let's blow it away!
ね？この湿気、吹き飛ばそう！
Right? Let's blow away this humidity!
もう一回行くよ？
Let's go one more time!
すいちゃんは～？
Sui-chan is...?
行けるやないの！
See, you can do it!
この後も最後まで喉枯らしていってくださいね！
Please keep shouting until you lose your voice till the very end!
ワンス・アポン・ア・ステラの物語は まだまだ始まったばかりです
The story of "Once Upon a Stella" has only just begun.
みんな 最後までついてきてください
Everyone, please stay with me until the very end.
それでは 次の曲にいきたいと思います
Now then, I'd like to move on to the next song.
聴いてください
Please listen.
光がひとつ灯った 灯った 天を彩った描写が綺麗だ
A light flickered on and shone, beautifully coloring the sky.
僕の吐いた白い息のように 消してしまえただろうな
Just like my white breath in the cold, I wish I could fade it away.
押し殺して深く沈んだ 泣き声が聞こえているか
Can you hear the sound of crying, stifled and sunken deep down?
君を刺した不安の鋲も
Even the shoes of anxiety that pierced you...
僕の破片を拾って 塗りつぶして全部無駄になって
Picking up my fragments, painting over them, it all became pointless,
星の海へ流れていった
and drifted away into the sea of stars.
果てしない闇の中に そっと手を添えたなら
If I gently place my hand into the endless darkness...
彗星が僕の頭上を飛んだ
A comet flew right over my head,
誰もいない夜の空を染めた
staining the empty night sky.
深海に沈んだ街の中で 降り注ぐのは誰の悲しみだろう
In a city sunken deep underwater, whose sorrow is raining down?
星はまた尾を描いて飛んだ
The star flew again, leaving a trailing tail behind,
靄のかかった思考を払って
clearing away my hazy thoughts.
いつか君に会えるなんて言えなかった 星が降った後の夜
On the night after stars fell, I couldn't say I'd meet you again someday.
黒く濁った銀河の底を 箒星が彩るように
As if a comet illuminates the bottom of a dark, murky galaxy...
君を刺した不安の鋲も
Even the shoes of anxiety that pierced you...
僕の破片を拾って 塗りつぶして君の指をそっと
Picking up my fragments, painting over them, gently wrapping your fingers...
星の海に抱き込んだ
embracing them into the sea of stars.
あの日見たその光が 誰かをまた救うから
Because the light we saw that day will save someone once more,
彗星が僕らの夜を照らした
a comet lit up our night.
この空を全部君にあげる
I will give this whole sky to you.
言えなかった言葉の重みで 降り注ぐのは誰の悲しみだろう
Weighing down from words unsaid, whose sorrow is raining down?
星はまた弧を描いて飛んだ
The star flew again, drawing an arc through the sky,
無知の視線が遮るように
as if blocking out ignorant gazes.
君とまた会えるから僕はこうだ 星の名前をひとつ受け止めよう
Because I'll meet you again, I stand here like this; I'll embrace the name of a star.
悲しみが溢れそうになること 天球で離れ離れでも
Even when sorrow seems about to overflow, even if we're apart in the celestial sphere...
僕らは繋がっているから
we are connected.
彗星が僕の頭上を飛んだ
A comet flew right over my head,
誰もいない夜の空を染めた
staining the empty night sky.
深海に沈んだ街の中で 降り注ぐのは誰の悲しみだろう
In a city sunken deep underwater, whose sorrow is raining down?
星はまた弧を描いて飛んだ
The star flew again, drawing an arc through the sky,
靄のかかった思考を払って
clearing away my hazy thoughts.
いつか君に会えるなんて言えなかった 星が降った後の夜
On the night after stars fell, I couldn't say I'd meet you again someday.
僕はずっと君の行方を探してた
I was searching for your whereabouts all along.
夜の底のファンタジー 散り散りになる像 像
Fantasy at the bottom of the night, images shattering into pieces.
本能のままに行動 孤独を取り囲む衝動
Acting on instinct, an impulse encircling solitude.
もう 誰だっていいや
At this point, anyone will do.
お互いの事を知りたいだけ
I just want to know about each other.
君が
You...
本当の気持ち
...your true feelings.
苦し紛れの言い訳はいらない 意味ない
I don't need desperate excuses, they're useless.
君はどう？
How about you?
正気を失ったみたいだな
Seems like you've lost your mind.
どこかおとぎの類で
Somewhere in a fairytale,
同じ言葉ばかり繰り返して
repeating the same words over and over,
鳥籠のなかで踊る
dancing inside a birdcage.
パッと過剰に作り繕うまでは
Until I dramatically over-embellish it,
泣き叫んで消えないように
crying out so I won't disappear,
魔法みたいな都合の良いものの
as the protagonist of something convenient
主人公なら 証言開示
like magic, disclosure of testimony!
最後はどうなってもハッピーエンド？
Is it a happy ending no matter what happens?
それなら好きにさせてよ 暴走したっていいわ
Then let me do as I like! I don't care if I run wild!
まさか罠に落ちていった？
Did I really fall into a trap?
無重力みたいな逃避行
An escape like weightlessness,
秘密のなか交わって飛んでいこう
mingling in secrets, let's fly away!
一切合切持っていって
Take everything away,
残虐な人生を謳歌
and enjoy this brutal life.
マジに合う星に思いを馳せて
Thinking of a star that truly suits us,
好きがないなんて この世はすべて終わった
Saying "there's no love", as if this world has ended,
アリホリック
Early-Holic!
もう どうなってもいいや
I don't care what happens anymore.
あんまりにも揺れてる
It's shaking way too much.
君の瞳の奥へとおびただしくてフォーカス
Focus intensely into the depths of your eyes.
大体だれだって真実の素顔見せるから
Basically anyone shows their true face,
だから爪を立て 簡単じゃないから
so dig your claws in, it's not simple at all!
もっともっともっともっと！
More, more, more, more!
うまく逃げ切って
Escape cleverly!
大空へと立つように 1、2、3で
Soaring into the big sky, 1, 2, 3!
これがルール 魔法みたいな都合の良いもの
That's the rule, something convenient like magic!
そんなの勝手！
Doing whatever I want with it!
諦めちゃってはもうバッドエンディング
Giving up leads straight to a bad ending!
確信の勇気を
The courage of conviction!
もうどうなってもいいや
I don't care what happens anymore!
火花みたいに燃えた証
The proof that burned like sparks,
いつの日か忘れちゃったの？
did you forget it somewhere along the way?
感情の絞り出しで特別になるんだろ
By wringing out our emotions, we become special, right?
惑わされ置き去りにされて
Deceived and left behind,
静寂と逃避行
a quiet escape.
かなり感じた距離まで引き寄せて
Pulling you close to the distance I felt,
月の涙が降った
tears of the moon fell.
この世はまるでストレンジャー 愛を叫べ
This world is like a stranger, shout out love!
まさか罠に落ちていった？
Did I really fall into a trap?
無重力みたいな逃避行
An escape like weightlessness,
秘密のなか交わって飛んでいこう
mingling in secrets, let's fly away!
一切合切持っていって
Take everything away,
残虐な人生を謳歌
and enjoy this brutal life.
マジに合う星に思いを馳せて
Thinking of a star that truly suits us,
好きがないなんて この世はすべて終わった
Saying "there's no love", as if this world has ended,
踊る終わりのファンタジー
Dancing end fantasy...
甘いシナリオ 乱されるざわめき 本能の赴くままに衝動
A sweet scenario, disturbed buzz, impulse following instinct!
もう どうなってもいいや
I don't care what happens anymore.
終わっちゃうし
It'll come to an end,
好きな人だっていなくなっちゃうんだ
and even the person I love will be gone.
寂しく
It makes me...
なっちゃうな
...feel lonely.
切実なことは
The pressing reality is,
ただひとつだけさ
there is only one thing:
もう後悔しないように
So that I won't regret anything anymore,
前を向いて生きるということ
I will face forward and keep living.
置いていく 置いていく 置いていく
Leaving it behind, leaving it behind...
どんな形で生まれてもスタイルを
No matter what shape I was born into, my style...
汚されたとしても気にしないよ
Even if it gets tarnished, I won't care.
だって私は私に恋していたいんだもん
Because I want to keep being in love with who I am.
愛してるよ 愛してるよ 愛してるよ
I love you, I love you, I love you,
サヨナラなんて涙が流れるけど
saying goodbye brings tears to my eyes, but...
何に依存したってしょうがないんだよ
there's no point in depending on anything.
この胸の この胸の痛みが
This pain in my heart...
愛だ
...is love.
今日も絡めるフェイク
Twisting through the fakes again today,
もう私 一周回って勇気だったりしないから
I won't come full circle into courage anymore,
自分を大切に出来ないんだ
because I can't cherish myself.
泣くくらいなら少し我慢するんだ
Rather than crying, I'll endure it a little.
今日も絡めるフェイク
Twisting through the fakes again today.
冒頭無料配信は終了いたしました。 配信チケットは概要欄から！
The free preview stream has ended. Stream tickets are available in the description!
The free opening stream has ended. Check the description section for tickets!